bradfordexchange.com 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy | The Bradford Exchange Online

Shopping online at this Website is extremely safe. We use secure Application Servers to protect your ordering information as it comes to us via the Internet. This means that all information, such as name, address and your credit card number you enter in the checkout section of our online store is encrypted. VeriSign provides authentication that you are in direct communication with this Website. 

If you have any concerns about ordering electronically, please call 1-866-907-3607 to place your order over the phone.

Collectibles Today Network, Ltd., which operates this Website, is an Internet marketing arm of The Bradford Group. We at the Bradford Group (identified below under "Information Sharing") are committed to protecting our customers' privacy. We know that you are concerned about how your information is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. The following notice describes our privacy policy.

Automatic Information:

This is information provided by cookies. Cookies are small alphanumeric identifier files that store information. They enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide important features that personalize our site to make your shopping faster and easier. For example they store your cart information between your visits. 

You can prevent your browser from accepting cookies through its help feature, but that prevents you from shopping on our site. We recommend that you take full advantage of all the features we've designed to make shopping easy and fun. 

Information That We Collect From Every Visitor:

We collect anonymous cookie information about the site pages, items, stores, and articles you view. This is not used with personally identifiable information (such as the name and address you give us when you place an order), but as aggregate information (group information) that helps us learn more about how people use and react to our site. We store information about the items you add to your cart so your cart selections are not lost between visits, but will not know who placed the items in the cart unless you send an order. 

We also send or permit collection of anonymous user information by service providers such as Coremetrics and ForeSee Results, who help us analyze information about user visits, and improve services. If you would like to change your settings or opt out of the Coremetrics service, please [click here](http://www.bradfordexchange.com/service/site-usage-statistics-settings.html). Note that by opting out of Coremetrics, you also opt out of ForeSee Results. 

Personal Information You Give Us Or Ask a Third Party to Send Us:

When you place an order, we will need your name, phone number, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number and expiration date so that we can process and contact you about the order. We will keep a record of this information and the items you purchase. This allows us to process and fulfill your orders and return requests, and to send you information that's of interest. 

You do not have to register at our site to place an order, but ordering is much simpler when you are registered. You will choose a login name and password that will allow you to update your personal information at any time in the future. When you log on with your password, your name, address and other contact information will automatically be entered into the correct spaces of your order form. Also, you can log on with your password, and track the status of orders you have given us. Our personal registration services are provided free of charge, and you are under no obligation to purchase anything.

For your convenience, we are adding “Log In With” links on our Website to certain social networking sites and browsers, starting with Facebook and Google. These links will allow you to log into this Website using your user name and password from the third party site to check the status of your prior orders from us or place new orders. This will save you the trouble of remembering a user name and password for our Website.

In order to synchronize your log-in on our Website with your log-in credentials from the other site, we will need to receive information from the other site that will enable us to verify that you are the account holder at both sites and facilitate your use of our Website. If you choose to access this Website with your log-in credentials from one of these linked sites, or if you otherwise agree to associate your account on our Website with one of these third party sites (for example, by choosing to join or “like” our page on the social networking site), that site will send us the personal information about you from your third party account that you authorize it to share with us, such as your username and password for that account, email address and other contact information, and social profile. We may add some or all of this shared information to our databases of information you submit to us when placing orders via The Bradford Group’s customer service center, US mail, or our websites and mobile applications. We will use and share that information in the ways disclosed below under “Information Sharing.” If you wish the third party site to discontinue sending information to us, you will need to notify the third party site of this election using the opt-out mechanisms offered by that site. This may require logging into your account with it and withdrawing your authorization to share information with us.

Surveys and Submissions

Periodically, this Website may ask customers to participate in surveys. If you participate, the information we collect may be associated with your account, and used to improve your overall customer experience. 

From time to time, we may ask you to post information showing how you have used our products. By contributing or submitting any content to this Website, and unless we indicate otherwise, you grant members of the Bradford Group a nonexclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, and fully sub licensable right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute and redistribute, and display such content throughout the world in any media, without compensation to you. You grant us the right to use the name (real or a pseudonym) and other identifying information that you submit in connection with such content, if we choose. When you transmit a submission you represent and warrant that you are 18 or older, own or otherwise control all of the rights to the content that you submit; that the content is accurate; that use of the content you supply does not violate this policy and will not cause injury to any person or entity; and that you will indemnify this Website and the Bradford Group for all claims resulting from content you supply. 

You agree that you shall not submit any information:

  * that is, or may reasonably be considered to be, defamatory, libelous, hateful, racially or religiously biased or offensive, unlawfully threatening, obscene, pornographic or profane material or any material that could constitute or encourage conduct that would be considered a criminal offense or give rise to civil liability, or otherwise violate any law, or unlawfully harassing to any individual, partnership or corporation; for which you were compensated or granted any consideration by any third party;
  * Or that contains any computer viruses, worms or other potentially damaging computer programs or files.

You acknowledge that The Bradford Group has sole discretion to publish, or not publish, your submissions in either the original or edited form. 

E-mail and Opting Out of E-mail:

When you order an item, a catalog, or have a customer service request, we send you an e-mail to confirm that we received your request or to answer your inquiry. These messages are generated automatically, and are sent regardless of "no-e-mail" requests. If you prefer not to receive other types of e-mail, you can opt out in the following ways:

  * Use the opt-out link at the bottom of every e-mail we send
  * Phone us at the number below and request to be opted out
  * Use our [contact us](http://www.bradfordexchange.com/service_contact-us.html) feature and request to be opted out
  * Mail us at the address below and request to be opted out

Please remember that if you add or change e-mail addresses, you need to separately notify us about your preferences for those e-mail addresses. 

Information Sharing:

This Website is one of a network of related companies who specialize in various high-quality collectible items such as collectors plates, dolls, figurines, ornaments and music boxes. Our affiliated companies or their divisions include:

  * The Bradford Exchange, Ltd.
  * The Bradford Exchange Checks, Ltd.
  * BGE, Ltd.

  * The Ashton-Drake Galleries, Ltd.
  * The Hamilton Collection, Inc.

Please note that our affiliates and divisions may change, and the list above may not be up-to-date. We sell products from our affiliates or their divisions and share information about your purchases with them. On occasion you may receive offers mailed by e-mail or ground mail from our affiliates or their divisions, or when you call our customer service department, for items that you may enjoy. We and our affiliates or their divisions may use information you provide when you order to personalize marketing communications to you. If you order from us or one of our affiliates or their divisions, we may share your e-mail address and other contact information for use in communications concerning your order and to offer other Bradford Group items that might interest you. You consent to this information sharing and use, and to being contacted by other companies in The Bradford Group.

We and our affiliates or their divisions also share certain collections of personal information that we regard as non-sensitive with selected third parties, such as mailing list brokers and database marketers. These entities may collect and use the information alone or in combination with customer information supplied by other companies, and share it with other companies for marketing purposes in the form of mailing lists. Our contracts with such third parties prohibit them from using or permitting use of the information we provide to generate reports about specific individuals, and require that they honor our customers' do-not-call, do-not-mail, and do-not-e-mail requests when our information is used. We and our affiliates or their divisions occasionally do ground mail list exchanges in which we provide mailing lists containing customer names and ground mail addresses to third parties in exchange for mailing lists with such information concerning the other company's customers. From time to time we or our affiliates or their divisions may use your ground mail address to send you offers that may interest you on behalf of third parties. If you respond to a third party offer you receive from us or from a company that has used a mailing list generated from our customer information, you will become that business's customer and the personal information you voluntarily submit to it will be subject to that company's privacy policy, not ours.

We do not exchange or share our customer e-mail addresses with third parties for marketing or promotional purposes.

If you object to our sharing information about you as a customer with these affiliated and non-affiliated companies or divisions, or if you prefer not to receive ground mail from us or other companies, you may use the [Contact Us](http://www.bradfordexchange.com/service_contact-us.html) feature on our site, or phone us at 1-866-907-3607 to tell us about your preferences. 

Even if you opt out from information sharing generally, we must share information about your individual orders with the sister corporation that packs, ships and bills your purchases, and with outside companies on a confidential basis as needed to obtain approval to charge your credit card, to verify your address, and to deliver your orders. 

When you visit our Website from a link on another Website, or in an ad or e-mail, a cookie will be placed on your computer, and if you make a purchase, information may be provided to the referring Website. This information is not personally identifiable. This will occur even if you opt out from other types of information sharing. Cookies placed on your computer when you visit our site may also be used to display banner ads concerning our items when you visit certain third party sites. 

We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of our Websites, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection, collecting unpaid purchase balances, and reducing credit risks. This protects you from price increases related to uncollected debt. 

Our business referral program is provided by an outside company. If you choose to use this optional service, then they may share your information with us, but are not authorized to contact you or provide your information to others, without your permission. 

Children:

This Website is a shopping site for mature collectors. We do not knowingly solicit or collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 years that is submitted to us via the Internet. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from a user under the age of 13, we will use reasonable measures to delete the information from our records as soon as it is discovered by us and do not use such information for any purpose (except where necessary to protect the safety of the child or others as required or allowed by law). If you become aware of any personally identifiable information we have collected from children under 13, please contact us at (866) 907-3607. 

Customer Information Transfer:

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses and assets, including customer information. 

Visit Us Often:

Please visit this Privacy Policy frequently, as our business changes all the time, and we update this policy to reflect those changes. By visiting our site you agree that we may collect and use information as stated in our privacy policy. If we change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page so you are always informed about what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

You can always reach us by [e-mail](http://www.bradfordexchange.com/service_contact-us.html), phone, or ground mail:

**By E-mail:**  

**By Ground Mail:  
The Bradford Exchange Online**  
9333 N. Milwaukee Avenue  
Niles, Illinois 60714

**By Phone:**  
United States: 1-866-907-3607  
Monday - Friday (excluding major holidays)  
7:00 A.M. - 6:00 P.M., Central Time
